<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="training_puzzle_clues">
        <item>1. Amy likes bananas.</item>
        <item>2. Belle isn\'t 10.</item>
        <item>3. The 9 years old girl likes grapes.</item>
        <item>4. Belle likes apples.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="snail_races_clues">
        <item>1. Of Todd and the snail with the teal shell, one finished in 24 minutes and the other is from Mexico.
</item>
        <item>2. The snail from Mexico finished 3 minutes after the snail with the lime shell, who finished 1 minute before the snail with the silver shell (who wasn\'t Hank).
</item>
        <item>3. The snail from USA finished 2 minutes before Kipp, who finished some time before the snail from Spain.
</item>
        <item>4. Of Ralph and the Spain contestant one had the fastest time and the other had the violet shell.
</item>
        <item>5. The snail from Canada was either the one with the teal shell or the one who finished in 25 minutes.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ballroom_dancing_clues">
       <item>1. Bradley (who didn\'t do the jitterbug) isn\'t Mr. Northrop.
</item>
       <item>2. Phyllis\'s surname is Moylan
</item>
       <item>3. Neither Margaret (who isn\'t Ms. Northrop) nor Audrey is either the woman who danced the jitterbug with Mr. Levy (who isn\'t Nathan) or the one who danced the tango with her companion.
</item>
       <item>4. Stewart (who isn\'t surnamed Levy) isn\'t the man who danced the fox trot and Vanessa wasn\'t his partner.
</item>
       <item>5. Neither Audrey nor the woman who danced a stunning waltz is married to Mr. Powell (who isn\'t Bradley).
</item>
       <item>6. Lorraine didn\'t dance the tango.
</item>
       <item>7. Audrey isn\'t Ms. Northrop and Margaret isn\'t the woman who danced the mambo with her husband.
</item>
       <item>8. Andrew\'s last name is Kavanaugh.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="late_at_the_lake_clues">
       <item>1. The friend who brought cake arrived at the lake seven minutes
           after the health-conscious girl who brought apples.</item>
       <item>2. Don did not bring lettuce.</item>
       <item>3. Kay arrived more than 10 minutes before the ham did, and immediately after the chips.</item>
       <item>4. Paul got to Bear Lake seven minutes after Don, but more than ten minutes before the crackers.</item>
       <item>5. The friend who went to the wrong spot brought cheese and arrived seven minutes ahead of the cake.</item>
       <item>6. Becky was seven minutes behind the tomatoes.</item>
       <item>7. Gary had a flat tire and arrived later than the chips.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="apple_pickers_clues">
    <item>1. The recipes, in no particular order, were the recipe using cinnamon,
        the recipe using three apples, the apple tarts, the recipe using Macoun apples, and the apple crisp.
        </item>
    <item>2. The recipe using the Cortland apples used one apple more than the
        apple bread but one apple less than the recipe using the raisins.
    </item>
    <item>3. The muffins used one more apple than the recipe with the
        walnuts but two less apples than the recipe using the Red Delicious apples.
</item>
    <item>4. The nutmeg was used in the apple crisp,
        which used more than two apples but less than the apple pie used.
        The apple pie used more apples than the treat with the raisins.
</item>
    <item>5. The apple muffins, which weren\'t made with Macoun apples, used pecans.
</item>
    <item>6. The Empire apples weren\'t used in the apple crisp. The recipe using the McIntosh apples used the most apples.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="vanishing_actors_clues">
        <item>1. A cast member suffered from laryngitis at some point later in the week than an understudy took over the role of Nick.
</item>
        <item>2. The actor playing George was absent exactly two days before the one who was away filming a movie.
</item>
        <item>3. Blair Diaz missed a performance at some point earlier in the week than the person portraying Martha (who wasn\'t off filming a movie).
</item>
        <item>4. Devon Rochan wasn\'t the last actor to miss a performance.
</item>
        <item>5. Reese DeWitt was replaced by an understudy exactly two days before an actor serving jury duty was sequestered overnight and couldn\'t perform.
</item>
    </string-array>

   <string-array name="bound_for_canada_clues">
       <item>1. Flight 444 departs at some point before flight 303 (which is Louis\' flight).
</item>
       <item>2. Franz\'s flight, which is going to Montreal, does not leave at either 10:00 a.m. or 2:00 p.m.
</item>
       <item>3. Flight 707 is destined for Quebec City. The flight to Vancouver (which isn\'t Heather\'s flight) leaves at precisely 11:00 a.m.
</item>
       <item>4. Sylvester\'s flight leaves at some point before flight 222 (which isn\'t Franz\'s flight).
</item>
       <item>5. Flight 505 is Maple Leaf Air\'s last one for the day. The flight to Toronto leaves at exactly 1:00 p.m.
</item>
    </string-array>


 <string-array name="secret_in_stone_clues">
       <item>1. Neither the opal necklace nor the piece set with a moonstone is the patchouli-scented item (which wasn\'t created by Dr. Ruth).
</item>
       <item>2. Dr. Phil\'s piece of jewelry is neither the lavender-scented one nor the rose-scented item.
</item>
       <item>3. The amethyst (which wasn\'t placed in the ring altered by Dr. Zhivago) wasn\'t set in the pair of earrings Dr. Seuss altered.
</item>
       <item>4. Dr. Spock is neither the scientist who worked on the brooch nor the one who fashioned the necklace.
</item>
       <item>5. Dr. Seuss scented his jewelry with musk. A garnet was set in Dr. Ruth\'s piece.
</item>
       <item>6. The piece set with moonstone (which isn\'t rose-scented) isn\'t the pair of earrings.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="on_the_canal_clues">
        <item>1. Bill\'s barge, which carried sand, was not named after a woman. His horse was not Star.</item>
        <item>2. Buck, who did not belong to Bob, pulled The Elizabeth.</item>
        <item>3. Fred owned The Mermaid.</item>
        <item>4. Ted\'s horse was Rosie but his barge was not The English Rose (which carried coal).</item>
        <item>5. George\'s barge did not carry slate.</item>
        <item>6. Itchy pulled the barge carrying Iron.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="flour_power_clues">
       <item>1. The cupcakes were served the day after the dessert made with wheat flour. The turnovers were made on Friday.
</item>
        <item>2. Kristen used rice flour to make Wednesday\'s dessert (which wasn\'t cupcakes).
</item>
        <item>3. The barley flour dessert was served later in the week than the cookies, which weren\'t Monday\'s dessert.
</item>
        <item>4. The brownies were made with oat flour.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="payday_clues">
        <item>1. The secretary makes the least amount of money, and has worked there the shortest amount of time.</item>
        <item>2. Jill makes less than the catering manager, but has worked there longer than everyone but the general manager.</item>
        <item>3. The Sales Manager position pays $800.00.</item>
        <item>4. The Administrative Assistant has worked there for 12 years.</item>
        <item>5. The General Manager makes the most money because he has the highest position with the most experience.</item>
        <item>6. Carla makes the least amount of money.</item>
        <item>7. Laurie is the catering manager.</item>
        <item>8. Warren has worked there for 10 years.</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="last_year_gifts_clues">
        <item>1. The four girls are Diana, the girl who has a birthday in February,
           the girl who received the diamond ring, and Allison.</item>
        <item>2. Christine received the ring in October, but it wasn\'t from Tom or Dave.</item>
        <item>3. Betty is allergic to flowers, so her boyfriend, Tom, knew not to get them for her.</item>
        <item>4. Dave gave the bracelet to his girlfriend in August, and Bill proposed in October.</item>
        <item>5. Allison\'s boyfriend did not buy flowers for her.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fortune_teller_name_clues">
        <item>1. Geneeva revealed to Greg (who is neither the Leo nor the Virgo) that he would soon meet his true love.</item>
        <item>2. Whitney isn\'t the woman born under the sign of Cancer (who was told to prepare for a trip to a faraway land).</item>
        <item>3. The Virgo isn\'t the one whom Geneeva predicted would inherit a large sum of money.</item>
        <item>4. Beth was pleased to hear that she would receive an important promotion at work.
</item>
        <item>5. A surprise visit from a long-lost relative was foretold for the Taurus woman.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="world_domination_clues">
      <item>1. The four potions were: the one given to Jessica, the one containing gardenia,
          the one containing rose, and the one that made its victim charming.</item>
      <item>2. The two boys each had a potion made partly from a tree with three letters.</item>
      <item>3. The daffodil was in the invisibility potion.</item>
      <item>4. Cassandra and Alfred each had a potion with a flower that started with the same letter.</item>
      <item>5. When the elm and daisy were mixed together, they did not make a poison.</item>
      <item>6. The potion which allows you to fly was created by plants which have the letter "o" in them.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="never_ask_a_woman_her_age_clues">
        <item>1. Jennifer\'s name is not Malone.</item>
        <item>2. Kate is twice as old as Lewis, but only half as old as Shannon.</item>
        <item>3. Jessica is 10 years older than Mrs. Smith, but 10 years younger than Mrs. Peterson.</item>
        <item>4. Janice is 20 years older than Kate and 20 years younger than Mrs. Ware.</item>
        <item>5. Kate is 10 years younger than Jessica but 20 years older than Jennifer.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="commuter_problems_clues">
        <item>1. Neither of the women took public transportation.</item>
        <item>2. Mary is still fuming over that faulty traffic signal.</item>
        <item>3. The rider on two wheels (who wasn\'t Carrie) decided to wait out the storm.</item>
        <item>4. Harry passed Carrie (who wasn\'t affected by construction or the storm) on his way to work.
            She later caught up to him because he forgot to pack his air pump.</item>
        <item>5. Jerry hoped to bypass other vehicles on the road by letting someone else
            drive, but the construction delays were too much.</item>
        <item>6. Larry and Mary worked too far away to walk to work and were glad they had full tanks of gas.
</item>
        <item>7. The walker was an eyewitness to an accident and had to wait around to give a statement to police.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="miss_brown_murder_clues">
        <item>1. Mr. Blues was in the kitchen when Miss Brown was murdered.</item>
        <item>2. The person with the sword was in the study the whole time.</item>
        <item>3. Countess Marigold wasn\'t in the hall and didn\'t have the rope.</item>
        <item>4. Both ladies didn\'t have access to a weapon with a blade.</item>
        <item>5. Sir Red was in the study for the evening.</item>
        <item>6. There was a magnificent candelabra in Miss Pinkham\'s room.</item>
        <item>7. The person in the kitchen had a dagger.</item>
        <item>8. Mr. Whitehall wasn\'t in the lounge or the porch.</item>
        <item>9. The person with the bit of plumbing most accessible was on the porch.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nighty_night_clues">
        <item>1. The girls are Rose, the girl that likes purple,
            the one that has a stuffed rabbit, and the person that has two pillows.</item>
        <item>2. Chelsea doesn\'t have the most pillows or the least.
</item>
        <item>3. The girl with the most pillows also has a stuffed rabbit.
</item>
        <item>4. Gabi feels snug in the most pillows.
</item>
        <item>5. Rose has a blue bear to match her comforter.
</item>
        <item>6. Daphne and Chelsea both have animals that begin with the same letter as their name.
</item>
        <item>7. Daphne\'s favorite color is orange and Chelsea has three pillows.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="moving_to_london_clues">
        <item>1. When I was young, I was taught to plant and
            grow flowers by the only aunt whose name contains a C, so she gave me things to plant in my new garden.</item>
        <item>2. The first gift I was given, at the airport, was so I could always find my way home.</item>
        <item>3. The sewing box was not given last although it was given after the seeds.</item>
        <item>4. Aunt Helen always told stories about how I would simply
            devour the written word, so she gave me plenty of volumes to read.</item>
        <item>5. The books were the only gift whose first letter corresponded
            to its place in the alphabet and to the order in which it was given.</item>
        <item>6. The last gift I received was from Aunt Patsy.
            She told me to "never quit believing that there was
            good in all," and that "teaching is the noblest of professions.
            For while teachers do not make millions, they do make tomorrow\'s leaders."</item>
        <item>7. Aunt Gail cannot sew, so grandmother did not give her the sewing box.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="murder_at_brainteaser_clues">
        <item>1. The person who "allegedly" used the poison was a female. </item>
        <item>2. Mrs. Red\'s motive was "supposedly" money.</item>
        <item>3. The motive of the person who used the rope was jealousy.</item>
        <item>4. Mr. Crimson "apparently" used the gun but his motive wasn\'t revenge.</item>
        <item>5. Lady Scarlet was believed to have used the rope.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="why_clues">
       <item>1. Camille was killed by another girl because of a silly bet made earlier that day.</item>
       <item>2. Kaleb killed his victim by accident.</item>
       <item>3. Liz killed Kaylee in a lime green room out of a sudden burst of rage from the wall hangings she noticed in the kitchen.</item>
       <item>4. Aviva killed her victim in the garden and won five hundred dollars.</item>
       <item>5. Tyler was killed by a flying book that
           struck him in the back of his head. Later his killer was upset by the news of Tyler\'s death.</item>
       <item>6. Kaylee was found dead on the toilet.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="office_order_clues">
      <item>1. The projector is not the most expensive item; however, it\'s not cheapest either.</item>
      <item>2. The paper costs $55 per carton through Recycling Co.</item>
      <item>3. The binders are the most expensive and are not ordered from Office Chain; however, the cheapest item is.</item>
      <item>4. The most expensive item is not ordered from Presentation Co.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paintballing_weekend_clues">
        <item>1. Brenda used blue paint balls.</item>
        <item>2. The person in the green T-shirt used yellow paint balls.</item>
        <item>3. James was not wearing a red T-shirt.</item>
        <item>4. Diane used green paint balls and wore a blue T-shirt.</item>
        <item>5. Simon was the only person who used paint which was the same colour as his T-shirt.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sandbox_disaster_clues">
        <item>1. The child with the dump truck is not Chris or Zach.</item>
        <item>2. Monica\'s son brought a bucket, but his name is not Tim.</item>
        <item>3. Lisa\'s daughter shares a first initial with her mother and she brought a shovel along.</item>
        <item>4. The doll belongs to Abbie\'s daughter.</item>
        <item>5. Zach is Marie\'s son.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hogwarts_clues">
        <item>1. Shelby is VERY smart.</item>
        <item>2. Billy is a scaredy cat.</item>
        <item>3. Billy and the boy in Slytherin took under a minute to be sorted.</item>
        <item>4. Billy always keeps promises and is not very bright.</item>
        <item>5. The person in Gryffindor took the longest.</item>
        <item>6. Anthony was the fastest to be sorted.</item>
        <item>7. Billy was sorted 30 seconds faster than the Ravenclaw.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jungle_gym_hoopla_clues">
        <item>1. Pete bought his son black shoes, but his son is neither Chris or Tim.</item>
        <item>2. Chris hates the colors green and pink, but his friend Laura loves green.</item>
        <item>3. Sam, Tim\'s dad, was searching for shoes the same color as a firetruck</item>
        <item>4. Kaleb and Zander are the only dads with daughters.</item>
        <item>5. Natalie\'s dad is not Kaleb.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="who_ate_which_fruit_clues">
        <item>1. The person that had the orange ate it on Saturday.</item>
        <item>2. The woman who had the apple did not eat it on Tuesday.</item>
        <item>3. Joseph did not eat the bananas and did not eat on Friday.</item>
        <item>4. People with O in their name did not eat the orange.</item>
        <item>5. Bob ate his fruit on Tuesday.</item>
        <item>6. Jenny loved eating her orange.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="family_trips_clues">
        <item>1. Neither Alexandra nor Cliff planned the 2003 trip.</item>
        <item>2. Ezekiel didn\'t plan a trip to Niagara Falls.</item>
        <item>3. Hazel picked the 2002 destination.</item>
        <item>4. Alexandra planned a trip to Gardens.</item>
        <item>5. Neither Ezekiel nor Hazel planned the trip to Williamsburg.</item>
        <item>6. A boy planned the 2004 vacation trip.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="just_a_thought_clues">
    <item>1. The students were not studying subjects that
        started with the same letter as their names.</item>
    <item>2.The one who checked out the books on Journalism, checked out an even number of books.</item>
    <item>3. The number of books about history was not a square number.</item>
    <item>4.When he\'s not writing papers on the fall of Rome,
        Sebastian likes to read about ancient civilizations.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draconia_trainers_clues">
        <item>1. The four people are: the one who owns the Red Dragon,
            the one who owns Brookzhay, the one who owns the Gold Dragon, and Crystal.</item>
        <item>2. Lillie thinks Aero and Brookzhay
            are nice-looking dragons, but prefers her own, the Gold Dragon.</item>
        <item>3. Harley\'s dragon is the fastest, but Aero is right behind.</item>
        <item>4. Even though Skae\'s name sounds like "Sky", she is not the color of the sky, day or night.</item>
        <item>5. Reikke, the Gold Dragon, wishes she belonged to Crystal because she gives her dragon more treats.</item>
        <item>6. Harley thinks she\'s cool because her dragon is the color of the night, but Geneva thinks her dragon, Skae, is much cooler.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multicolour_doors_clues">
        <item>1. Carly just loves the colour pink and she was ecstatic when her mom painted the door for her.</item>
        <item>2. Alan\'s always around at Harry\'s house. It\'s easy to get there because Oak St is only just around the corner from Alan\'s house.</item>
        <item>3. South Ave has mostly white doors, so the red one, belonging to one of the friends, stands out easily to the passing cars.</item>
        <item>4. Alan thinks that his friend\'s blue door clashes badly with their house but he doesn\'t want to tell them in case he hurts their feelings.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="snack_time_clues">
        <item>1. Of course, Rachel remembered that she wanted milk and orange slices</item>
        <item>2. Although she couldn\'t remember who it was, Rachel knew that the person who wanted juice also wanted apple slices</item>
        <item>3. Rachel knew that Sophie didn\'t like apples</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mates_plus_dates_clues">
        <item>1. 5:45 \n Can\'t believe how cold it is and the grass is all wet, yuck. It\'s okay though, Matt gave me his coat, I think he really likes me.</item>
        <item>2. 8:34 \n Hey guys, hope you\'re having a better time than I am. Ben is such a bore, I don\'t think I\'ll be doing this again. xoxoxo love, Sarah oxoxox</item>
        <item>3. 9:24 \n Wow, this movie is fantastic and he\'s just as into it as I am. I don\'t think it\'d ever be as fun with a geek like Matt (no offence). I don\'t ever want this to end. Good luck on your dates, love Natalie</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="more_painters_clues">
        <item>1. Painter 3 painted his house white.
        </item>
        <item>2. House 1 wasn\'t painted green or yellow.
        </item>
        <item>3. Painters 1 and 4 didn\'t use green or blue paint.
        </item>
        <item>4. Houses 1, 3 and 5 weren\'t painted brown.
        </item>
        <item>5. Painters 2, 4 and 5 didn\'t use brown paint.
        </item>
        <item>6. Houses 1, 3 and 4 weren\'t painted white.
        </item>
        <item>7. Painter 2 didn\'t use green or yellow paint.
        </item>
        <item>8. Houses 2 and 5 weren\'t painted green.
        </item>
        <item>9. Houses 3 and 4 weren\'t painted yellow.
        </item>
        <item>10. House 2 was not painted white.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kittens_and_kids_clues">
        <item>1. Catapult weighs more than the kitten taken by Martha.
        </item>
        <item>2. The kitten that weighs 17 oz. is not Bandit.
        </item>
        <item>3. Codi weighs just under a pound but is not the lightest.
        </item>
        <item>4. Kurt\'s kitten is not Bandit.
        </item>
        <item>5. Ted\'s kitten is not the largest, but weighs over a pound.
        </item>
        <item>6. Hallie weighs less than Codi.
        </item>
        <item>7. Martha\'s kitten weighs 14 oz.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jazz_band_solos_clues">
        <item>1. Maria\'s solo was unique. She sang as she played.
        </item>
        <item>2. Steve\'s last name sounded like the instrument he played.
        </item>
        <item>3. Mr. Wilson played his solo before the tenor sax player.
        </item>
        <item>4. Will played his trumpet during the fifth solo.
        </item>
        <item>5. Ms Earl, who didn\'t play trombone, played her solo before Steve but after Ms Lewis.
        </item>
        <item>6. The alto sax was featured in the first solo.
        </item>
        <item>7. Lucy played a brass instrument.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>