<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="training_puzzle_story">Follow the clues to determine which fruit does the oldest girl like.</string>

    <string name="sandbox_disaster_story">
        Five mothers decided to take their adorable children to the park.
        Each woman allowed her child to bring one toy. All the children raced
        to the sandbox with their toy. They had so much fun in the sandbox
        that all the toys got mixed up, and each mother lost track of her
        child. Can you help them sort this mess out so each child goes home
        with the correct toy, and each parent goes home with the correct child?
    </string>

    <string name="hogwarts_story">A group of soon-to-be-first-years at Hogwarts
        School of Witchcraft and Wizardry just walked into the Great Hall.
        Everybody has been sorted into a house of either Slytherin, Hufflepuff,
        Gryffindor, or Ravenclaw. Hufflepuff = Loyal and Trustworthy;
        Ravenclaw = cunning and intelligent; Gryffindor = brave and noble;
        Slytherin = keen and ambitious.
        There are still 4 kids to be sorted. Their names are Billy, Shelby,
        Anthony, and Kristen. The sorting hat takes some time for each kid.
        Find out the amount of time the hat took and which house each kid ended up in.</string>

    <string name="jungle_gym_hoopla_story">After the sandbox disaster the week before,
        five fathers were in charge of taking the children to the park.
        The fathers did not want to have the same mix-up with the
        sandbox that their wives went through, so this week they
        kept all their children on the jungle gym. Everything
        was going good until it was time to leave and the kids
        had to put their shoes on. It was at that time that the
        fathers realized that the shoes were all mixed up. Can
        you help these fathers figure out which shoes belong to which child?</string>

    <string name="family_trips_story">The Fennings encourage their
        four children to take the lead in planning family events.
        In each of the last four years, a different child has planned
        a different place he or she wanted to go. Can you determine
        the year each child came up with a vacation plan and what destination he or she chose?</string>

    <string name="who_ate_which_fruit_story">There are 4 people - Jenny, Bob, Kate and Joseph.
        They each had a piece of fruit - Orange, Apple, Grapes and Banana.
        On a certain day - Monday, Friday, Saturday, Tuesday.
        Can you work out who has which fruit on which day?</string>

    <string name="just_a_thought_story">Three friends were studying at the library.
        Their names were Helga, Johannes, and Sebastian.
        Each person was studying a different subject (History, Journalism, and Science)
        and checked out a different number of books (2, 5, and 9.)
        The computer at the library was down for repairs that day.
        The Librarian wrote down the titles of the books and the names of the students.
        The next day when the computer was back on-line she had forgotten who checked
        out how many books and on which topic. Can you help her get this sorted out?</string>

    <string name="draconia_trainers_story">Once, in a faraway land called Dracoria,
        four girls - Lillie, Harley, Crystal, and Geneva - were becoming dragon trainers.
        They each got a different-colored dragon and named it something different. Using
        the clues, can you figure out who had which dragon and what she named it?</string>

    <string name="multicolour_doors_story">Three friends all live in houses with painted doors.
        Can you use these clues to find out what colour door they have and what road they live on?    </string>

    <string name="snack_time_story">One day, Rachel had her two best friends over
        for a play date. When it came time for a snack, her mom
        asked her to find out what everyone wanted. Rachel was happy
        to help because she loved playing hostess. However, when Rachel
        got back to her mom, she couldn\'t quite remember everything. Can you help her figure it out?</string>

    <string name="mates_plus_dates_story">Three girls all got dates on the same day. From their
        texts, can you figure out which girl went with which guy and where they went on their dates.</string>

    <string name="more_painters_story">At the Painted House painting company they have 5 painters.
        The home-owners can choose from 5 paint colors; white, green, blue, yellow and brown.
        Can you figure out which painter painted which house with which color?</string>

    <string name="kittens_and_kids_story">Four kittens weigh four pounds together,
        but they don\'t weigh one pound each. No, no, that would make this puzzle
        too easy for such a smart person as you! Two of the kittens weigh
        less than a pound and two of them weigh more than a pound. Four
        kids come along and take the four kittens. Makes sense,
        the kittens being really cute and all! So, see if you c
        an figure out which kid takes which kitten and how much
        each one weighs (no, not the kids… the kittens) from the clues presented below.</string>

    <string name="jazz_band_solos_story">
        Evan, Lucy, Maria, Steve,
        and Will all played together in a local jazz band.
        At their last concert, they each had a solo. Match
        the musicians with their last name, instrument, and order they played.</string>
</resources>