<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="training_puzzle_story">Follow the clues to determine which fruit does the oldest girl like.</string>

    <string name="last_year_gifts_story">
        Four friends were talking about what their boyfriends gave
        them as a birthday present last year. Using the clues below,
        determine who their boyfriends are, when their birthdays are, and what they received.
    </string>

  <string name="flour_power_gifts_story">
    While studying to be a nutritionist, Kristen learned
      of the many health benefits of using alternate
      types of flour — but convincing her family was another matter!
      To win them over, Kristen prepared a different type of dessert
      (including beignets) each weekday last week, each time using a different type of flour.
      After tasting her delicacies, Kristen\'s family didn\'t complain any longer —
      they were too busy eating! From the information provided, determine the type
      of flour used to make dessert she served on each week day.
    </string>

    <string name="on_the_canal_story">
        Five barges, The Marianna, The Elizabeth,
        The English Rose, The Blackbird, and The Mermaid,
        were on a canal. Each was pulled by a different
        horse, Rosie, Star, Buck, Prince, and Itchy, and
        carried a different cargo, coal, gravel, iron,
        sand, and slate. Each barge was owned by either
        Bob, Bill, Fred, George or Ted.
    </string>

    <string name="payday_story">
        The new accountant is putting together payroll.
        She is having a hard time remembering who does what in the office,
        which makes it hard to print out the pay checks. This is what she does know.
    </string>

    <string name="office_order_story">
        Monica\'s boss asked her to order some supplies for
        an important project. While organizing her desk,
        she spilled her coffee all over her ordering list.
        The list was soaked and partially unreadable. Please help Monica determine the ordering information.
    </string>

    <string name="fortune_teller_story">
        While at a carnival, five friends, Beth, Michelle, Whitney,
        Greg and Karl had their fortunes told by Geneeva the Seer.
        Each person gave Geneeva his or her astrological sign and
        she gazed into her crystal ball. She then predicted a different
        momentous event for each. From the information provided,
        determine each friend\'s sign and the event Geneeva had predicted:
    </string>


    <string name="world_domination_story">
        Mad Scientist Sassi the Sane was hell bent on taking over the world.
        Her latest plan was to mix together a number of plants to see what properties they contained.
        She managed to lure four unsuspecting people (Jessica, Nicholas, Cassandra and Alfred) into
        her secret cave. Once there she fed them each a type of tree
        (gumtree, oak, elm, gardenia) and a type of flower (tulip, rose, daffodil and daisy).
        Each tree/flower pairing created a different effect: one caused you to be able to fly;
        another caused you to turn invisible; one potion was poisonous; and one made you instantly charming.
        Can you determine which two plants were mixed together,
        what effect it had, and which hapless victim was forced to try it?
    </string>

    <string name="commuter_problems_story">
        Five friends (Men: Larry, Harry, and Jerry; Women: Carrie and Mary)
        each had trouble getting to work one day. Identify which friend
        used which mode of transport, and the corresponding reason they were late to work.
    </string>

    <string name="never_ask_a_woman_her_age_story">
        Jennifer, Shannon, Jessica, Kate, and Janice,
        whose last names are Peterson, Smith, Malone,
        Ware, and Lewis, all go to the same exercise gym.
        From the clues below, try to determine the first
        and last name of each woman and her age.
        Their ages are 80, 60, 50, 40, and 20
    </string>

    <string name="miss_brown_murder_story">
       Miss Brown was walking alone in her over-sized house, when suddenly a figure jumped out and killed her.
        "It is like a Cluedo case," commented Mr. Lombang, a detective. "Who killed her, what was their weapon,
        and where did they kill her?"
        The murderer would have been someone staying in Miss Brown\'s home.
        Therefore, it is either Mr. Blues, Sir Red, Mr. Whitehall, Countess Marigold, or Miss Pinkham.
        The weapons most likely to be used were a candelabra, a dagger, a plumbing piece, an ancient
        sword, or a piece of rope. The room in which Miss Brown was murdered was either the lounge,
        the kitchen, the porch, the hall, or the study. Now the detective Mr. Lombang must
        figure out who did it based on the following clues. Work out where everyone was:
        the person in the hall was the murderer.
    </string>

    <string name="nighty_night_story">
        While her four daughters were at camp,
        Mrs. Smith decided to clean their rooms for them.
        She vacuumed their floor, and washed their laundry and their bedclothes.
        When she took the laundry out of the dryer, she couldn\'t remember what went on which bed.
        She did, however, remember certain things about each girl that helped her. Can you figure it out?
    </string>

    <string name="moving_to_london_story">
        Last year, as I prepared to board the plane
        that would take me to my new home in London, my five
        aunts each gave me a gift. Each gift was something I
        had always cherished deeply. Charlotte, Patsy, Helen,
        Gail and Donna (in no particular order) gave me seeds
        to plant, advice, books, a map, and my grandmother\'s sewing box (in no particular order).
        Can you deduce from these clues, which aunt gave which gift and in what order?
    </string>

    <string name="murder_at_brainteaser_story">
      Four guests, Mrs. Red, Mr. Crimson, Lady Scarlet and Mr. Sienna, were all invited
        to an exclusive party at Brainteaser Mansion. However, during the long, dark night,
        the owner of the spectacular mansion, Mr. Death, was found dead in the library.
        Since no one apparently knew what happened, rumours were multiplying by the
        second, because everyone was suspected of killing him with a different weapon.
        From the following clues, can you work out who killed him?
    </string>

    <string name="why_story">Three people were killed in one night,
        in the same mansion, in three different rooms, and for three
        different reasons. The killers were Aviva, Kaleb, and Liz.
        They killed Camille, Tyler, and Kaylee. Based on the following clues,
        help Detective Miff find who killed whom and for what reason.</string>

    <string name="paintballing_weekend_story">
       During a crazy weekend of paintball, four friends were having great fun.
        The paint came in blue, green, yellow and red. Coincidentally, the four friends had T-shirts in those same colours.
        Can you tell which colour paint they each used and the colour of their respective T-shirts?
    </string>

    <string name="sandbox_disaster_story">
        Five mothers decided to take their adorable children to the park.
        Each woman allowed her child to bring one toy. All the children raced
        to the sandbox with their toy. They had so much fun in the sandbox
        that all the toys got mixed up, and each mother lost track of her
        child. Can you help them sort this mess out so each child goes home
        with the correct toy, and each parent goes home with the correct child?
    </string>

    <string name="hogwarts_story">A group of soon-to-be-first-years at Hogwarts
        School of Witchcraft and Wizardry just walked into the Great Hall.
        Everybody has been sorted into a house of either Slytherin, Hufflepuff,
        Gryffindor, or Ravenclaw. Hufflepuff = Loyal and Trustworthy;
        Ravenclaw = cunning and intelligent; Gryffindor = brave and noble;
        Slytherin = keen and ambitious.
        There are still 4 kids to be sorted. Their names are Billy, Shelby,
        Anthony, and Kristen. The sorting hat takes some time for each kid.
        Find out the amount of time the hat took and which house each kid ended up in.</string>

    <string name="jungle_gym_hoopla_story">After the sandbox disaster the week before,
        five fathers were in charge of taking the children to the park.
        The fathers did not want to have the same mix-up with the
        sandbox that their wives went through, so this week they
        kept all their children on the jungle gym. Everything
        was going good until it was time to leave and the kids
        had to put their shoes on. It was at that time that the
        fathers realized that the shoes were all mixed up. Can
        you help these fathers figure out which shoes belong to which child?</string>

    <string name="family_trips_story">The Fennings encourage their
        four children to take the lead in planning family events.
        In each of the last four years, a different child has planned
        a different place he or she wanted to go. Can you determine
        the year each child came up with a vacation plan and what destination he or she chose?</string>

    <string name="who_ate_which_fruit_story">There are 4 people - Jenny, Bob, Kate and Joseph.
        They each had a piece of fruit - Orange, Apple, Grapes and Banana.
        On a certain day - Monday, Friday, Saturday, Tuesday.
        Can you work out who has which fruit on which day?</string>

    <string name="just_a_thought_story">Three friends were studying at the library.
        Their names were Helga, Johannes, and Sebastian.
        Each person was studying a different subject (History, Journalism, and Science)
        and checked out a different number of books (2, 5, and 9.)
        The computer at the library was down for repairs that day.
        The Librarian wrote down the titles of the books and the names of the students.
        The next day when the computer was back on-line she had forgotten who checked
        out how many books and on which topic. Can you help her get this sorted out?</string>

    <string name="draconia_trainers_story">Once, in a faraway land called Dracoria,
        four girls - Lillie, Harley, Crystal, and Geneva - were becoming dragon trainers.
        They each got a different-colored dragon and named it something different. Using
        the clues, can you figure out who had which dragon and what she named it?</string>

    <string name="multicolour_doors_story">Three friends all live in houses with painted doors.
        Can you use these clues to find out what colour door they have and what road they live on?    </string>

    <string name="snack_time_story">One day, Rachel had her two best friends over
        for a play date. When it came time for a snack, her mom
        asked her to find out what everyone wanted. Rachel was happy
        to help because she loved playing hostess. However, when Rachel
        got back to her mom, she couldn\'t quite remember everything. Can you help her figure it out?</string>

    <string name="mates_plus_dates_story">Three girls all got dates on the same day. From their
        texts, can you figure out which girl went with which guy and where they went on their dates.</string>

    <string name="more_painters_story">At the Painted House painting company they have 5 painters.
        The home-owners can choose from 5 paint colors; white, green, blue, yellow and brown.
        Can you figure out which painter painted which house with which color?</string>

    <string name="kittens_and_kids_story">Four kittens weigh four pounds together,
        but they don\'t weigh one pound each. No, no, that would make this puzzle
        too easy for such a smart person as you! Two of the kittens weigh
        less than a pound and two of them weigh more than a pound. Four
        kids come along and take the four kittens. Makes sense,
        the kittens being really cute and all! So, see if you c
        an figure out which kid takes which kitten and how much
        each one weighs (no, not the kids… the kittens) from the clues presented below.</string>

    <string name="jazz_band_solos_story">
        Evan, Lucy, Maria, Steve,
        and Will all played together in a local jazz band.
        At their last concert, they each had a solo. Match
        the musicians with their last name, instrument, and order they played.</string>
</resources>