<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="training_puzzle_clues">
        <item>1. Amy likes bananas.</item>
        <item>2. Belle isn\'t 10.</item>
        <item>3. The 9 years old girl likes grapes.</item>
        <item>4. Belle likes apples..</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="moving_to_london_clues">
        <item>1. When I was young, I was taught to plant and
            grow flowers by the only aunt whose name contains a C, so she gave me things to plant in my new garden.</item>
        <item>2. The first gift I was given, at the airport, was so I could always find my way home.</item>
        <item>3. The sewing box was not given last although it was given after the seeds.</item>
        <item>4. Aunt Helen always told stories about how I would simply
            devour the written word, so she gave me plenty of volumes to read.</item>
        <item>5. The books were the only gift whose first letter corresponded
            to its place in the alphabet and to the order in which it was given.</item>
        <item>6. The last gift I received was from Aunt Patsy.
            She told me to "never quit believing that there was
            good in all," and that "teaching is the noblest of professions.
            For while teachers do not make millions, they do make tomorrow\'s leaders."</item>
        <item>7. Aunt Gail cannot sew, so grandmother did not give her the sewing box.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="murder_at_brainteaser_clues">
        <item>1. The person who "allegedly" used the poison was a female. </item>
        <item>2. Mrs. Red\'s motive was "supposedly" money.</item>
        <item>3. The motive of the person who used the rope was jealousy.</item>
        <item>4. Mr. Crimson "apparently" used the gun but his motive wasn\'t revenge.</item>
        <item>5. Lady Scarlet was believed to have used the rope.
</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="why_clues">
       <item>1. Camille was killed by another girl because of a silly bet made earlier that day.</item>
       <item>2. Kaleb killed his victim by accident.</item>
       <item>3. Liz killed Kaylee in a lime green room out of a sudden burst of rage from the wall hangings she noticed in the kitchen.</item>
       <item>4. Aviva killed her victim in the garden and won five hundred dollars.</item>
       <item>5. Tyler was killed by a flying book that
           struck him in the back of his head. Later his killer was upset by the news of Tyler\'s death.</item>
       <item>6. Kaylee was found dead on the toilet.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="office_order_clues">
      <item>1. The projector is not the most expensive item; however, it\'s not cheapest either.</item>
      <item>2. The paper costs $55 per carton through Recycling Co.</item>
      <item>3. The binders are the most expensive and are not ordered from Office Chain; however, the cheapest item is.</item>
      <item>4. The most expensive item is not ordered from Presentation Co.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="paintballing_weekend_clues">
        <item>1. Brenda used blue paint balls.</item>
        <item>2. The person in the green T-shirt used yellow paint balls.</item>
        <item>3. James was not wearing a red T-shirt.</item>
        <item>4. Diane used green paint balls and wore a blue T-shirt.</item>
        <item>5. Simon was the only person who used paint which was the same colour as his T-shirt.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sandbox_disaster_clues">
        <item>1. The child with the dump truck is not Chris or Zach.</item>
        <item>2. Monica\'s son brought a bucket, but his name is not Tim.</item>
        <item>3. Lisa\'s daughter shares a first initial with her mother and she brought a shovel along.</item>
        <item>4. The doll belongs to Abbie\'s daughter.</item>
        <item>5. Zach is Marie\'s son.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hogwarts_clues">
        <item>1. Shelby is VERY smart.</item>
        <item>2. Billy is a scaredy cat.</item>
        <item>3. Billy and the boy in Slytherin took under a minute to be sorted.</item>
        <item>4. Billy always keeps promises and is not very bright.</item>
        <item>5. The person in Gryffindor took the longest.</item>
        <item>6. Anthony was the fastest to be sorted.</item>
        <item>7. Billy was sorted 30 seconds faster than the Ravenclaw.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jungle_gym_hoopla_clues">
        <item>1. Pete bought his son black shoes, but his son is neither Chris or Tim.</item>
        <item>2. Chris hates the colors green and pink, but his friend Laura loves green.</item>
        <item>3. Sam, Tim\'s dad, was searching for shoes the same color as a firetruck</item>
        <item>4. Kaleb and Zander are the only dads with daughters.</item>
        <item>5. Natalie\'s dad is not Kaleb.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="who_ate_which_fruit_clues">
        <item>1. The person that had the orange ate it on Saturday.</item>
        <item>2. The woman who had the apple did not eat it on Tuesday.</item>
        <item>3. Joseph did not eat the bananas and did not eat on Friday.</item>
        <item>4. People with O in their name did not eat the orange.</item>
        <item>5. Bob ate his fruit on Tuesday.</item>
        <item>6. Jenny loved eating her orange.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="family_trips_clues">
        <item>1. Neither Alexandra nor Cliff planned the 2003 trip.</item>
        <item>2. Ezekiel didn\'t plan a trip to Niagara Falls.</item>
        <item>3. Hazel picked the 2002 destination.</item>
        <item>4. Alexandra planned a trip to Gardens.</item>
        <item>5. Neither Ezekiel nor Hazel planned the trip to Williamsburg.</item>
        <item>6. A boy planned the 2004 vacation trip.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="just_a_thought_clues">
    <item>1. The students were not studying subjects that
        started with the same letter as their names.</item>
    <item>2.The one who checked out the books on Journalism, checked out an even number of books.</item>
    <item>3. The number of books about history was not a square number.</item>
    <item>4.When he\'s not writing papers on the fall of Rome,
        Sebastian likes to read about ancient civilizations.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="draconia_trainers_clues">
        <item>1. The four people are: the one who owns the Red Dragon,
            the one who owns Brookzhay, the one who owns the Gold Dragon, and Crystal.</item>
        <item>2. Lillie thinks Aero and Brookzhay
            are nice-looking dragons, but prefers her own, the Gold Dragon.</item>
        <item>3. Harley\'s dragon is the fastest, but Aero is right behind.</item>
        <item>4. Even though Skae\'s name sounds like "Sky", she is not the color of the sky, day or night.</item>
        <item>5. Reikke, the Gold Dragon, wishes she belonged to Crystal because she gives her dragon more treats.</item>
        <item>6. Harley thinks she\'s cool because her dragon is the color of the night, but Geneva thinks her dragon, Skae, is much cooler.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multicolour_doors_clues">
        <item>1. Carly just loves the colour pink and she was ecstatic when her mom painted the door for her.</item>
        <item>2. Alan\'s always around at Harry\'s house. It\'s easy to get there because Oak St is only just around the corner from Alan\'s house.</item>
        <item>3. South Ave has mostly white doors, so the red one, belonging to one of the friends, stands out easily to the passing cars.</item>
        <item>4. Alan thinks that his friend\'s blue door clashes badly with their house but he doesn\'t want to tell them in case he hurts their feelings.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="snack_time_clues">
        <item>1. Of course, Rachel remembered that she wanted milk and orange slices</item>
        <item>2. Although she couldn\'t remember who it was, Rachel knew that the person who wanted juice also wanted apple slices</item>
        <item>3. Rachel knew that Sophie didn\'t like apples</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mates_plus_dates_clues">
        <item>1. 5:45 \n Can\'t believe how cold it is and the grass is all wet, yuck. It\'s okay though, Matt gave me his coat, I think he really likes me.</item>
        <item>2. 8:34 \n Hey guys, hope you\'re having a better time than I am. Ben is such a bore, I don\'t think I\'ll be doing this again. xoxoxo love, Sarah oxoxox</item>
        <item>3. 9:24 \n Wow, this movie is fantastic and he\'s just as into it as I am. I don\'t think it\'d ever be as fun with a geek like Matt (no offence). I don\'t ever want this to end. Good luck on your dates, love Natalie</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="more_painters_clues">
        <item>1. Painter 3 painted his house white.
        </item>
        <item>2. House 1 wasn\'t painted green or yellow.
        </item>
        <item>3. Painters 1 and 4 didn\'t use green or blue paint.
        </item>
        <item>4. Houses 1, 3 and 5 weren\'t painted brown.
        </item>
        <item>5. Painters 2, 4 and 5 didn\'t use brown paint.
        </item>
        <item>6. Houses 1, 3 and 4 weren\'t painted white.
        </item>
        <item>7. Painter 2 didn\'t use green or yellow paint.
        </item>
        <item>8. Houses 2 and 5 weren\'t painted green.
        </item>
        <item>9. Houses 3 and 4 weren\'t painted yellow.
        </item>
        <item>10. House 2 was not painted white.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kittens_and_kids_clues">
        <item>1. Catapult weighs more than the kitten taken by Martha.
        </item>
        <item>2. The kitten that weighs 17 oz. is not Bandit.
        </item>
        <item>3. Codi weighs just under a pound but is not the lightest.
        </item>
        <item>4. Kurt\'s kitten is not Bandit.
        </item>
        <item>5. Ted\'s kitten is not the largest, but weighs over a pound.
        </item>
        <item>6. Hallie weighs less than Codi.
        </item>
        <item>7. Martha\'s kitten weighs 14 oz.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jazz_band_solos_clues">
        <item>1. Maria\'s solo was unique. She sang as she played.
        </item>
        <item>2. Steve\'s last name sounded like the instrument he played.
        </item>
        <item>3. Mr. Wilson played his solo before the tenor sax player.
        </item>
        <item>4. Will played his trumpet during the fifth solo.
        </item>
        <item>5. Ms Earl, who didn\'t play trombone, played her solo before Steve but after Ms Lewis.
        </item>
        <item>6. The alto sax was featured in the first solo.
        </item>
        <item>7. Lucy played a brass instrument.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>